<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<updates>
  <update version="2.4.39.0">
    1. Fixed an issue where the focus would shift to another application when closing the update screen.
    2. Fixed internal process for creating TelnetClient.
    3. Changed to specify a separate timeout period for telnet logging.
    4. Fixed an issue processing of player and time acquisition.
      4.1. This solves the issue of output to the central log, such as player and time acquisition.
    5. Fixed internal processing of XmlEditor.
      5.1. Fixed an issue where XmlEditor could move to a layer above the root node in a drag move.
      5.2. Fixed an issue where drag moves in XmlEditor could be put into child elements other than tags.
    6. Added "Permission Editor" to edit serveradmin.xml.
  </update>
  <update version="2.3.38.4">
    1. Fixed an issue where getting a player or time would not work properly.
    2. Fixed an issue where the time setting button would not work properly.
    3. Fixed an issue where an error would occur when selecting an element in the Savannah Xml Editor.
    4. Fixed an issue where dragging a mouse move on an element in the Savannah Xml Editor would not work properly.
    5. Changed the connection to the update server.
      5.1. If you update from this version or earlier, it may take two updates.
    6. 32bit priority has been removed.
      6.1. On 64bit OS, it works as 64bit.
  </update>
  <update version="2.3.37.3">
    1. fixed an issue where the server could start if a Telnet connection failed even when local server mode is off.
    2. fixed an issue with stored addresses being rewritten when making a Telnet connection in local server mode.
    3. Moved Savannah Xml Editor from beta to stable version.
      3.1. Internal XML parser has been updated to <nobr /><a href="https://github.com/AonaSuzutsuki/SavannahXmlLib">SavannahXmlLib</a><nobr />.

    4. Fixed a bug that caused an error in the update check when it could not connect to the update server.
      4.1 An error dialog is display, but it works normally.
  </update>
  <update version="2.3.35.1">
    1. changed the wait time to asynchronous when it can't connect by Telnet.
    2. fixed the problem where there was an error when exiting Savannah Manager after the server exits.
  </update>
  <update version="2.3.34.0">
    1. Update system has been updated.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.33.6">
    1. add a19b compatible config template
    2. extended the text box for the number of days.
    3. fixed a problem where the message box was empty on the force end screen.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.32.5">
    1. fixed the problem that line feeds are not recognized correctly when getting the log of Telnet.
    2. the initial setup screen has been replaced with a new system
      This allows it to be skipped even when managing only other servers.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.31.4">
    1.　fixed an issue that telnet is not be able to connect after telnet is disconnected force.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.30.3">
    1. Added Xml Editor.
      1.1 Please enable beta mode from the settings, if you want to enable Xml Editor.
      1.2 Xml Editor can be started from the "Tool".
      1.3 You can run Xml Editor directly from executable file.
    2. Updated internal framework.
      1.1 Updated .Net Framework 4.7.1 to 4.8.
      1.2 Please install .Net Framework 4.8 before update this application.
    3. Fixed a problem that thorws exception when opening Admin/Whitelist/Kick/Ban

    <br />

    <font color="#ff0000">
      ○ Notice
      The target framework changed to .Net Framework 4.8 with this update.
      Please install Runtime if you don't install.
      You cannot launch this app if you don't install runtime.
    </font>
    <a href="https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-framework/net48">
      <font color="#00ffff">https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-framework/net48</font>
    </a>

    <br />

    I'm also considering moving from .Net Framework to .Net Core over time, so a different runtime may be required.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.29.2">
    1. Fixed template on ConfigEditor
      Fixed "DropOnDeath" value for a18.
      Fixed the English file was written in Japanese.
    2. Updated internal library.
    3. Added function to delete selected backup on BackupEditor
    4. Changed to be able to set the backup destination of Backup Editor individually
      You can change the save destination in the settings.

    ○ Notice
    The target framework changed to .Net Framework 4.8 with this update.
    Please install Runtime if you don't install.
    You cannot launch this app if you don't install runtime.
    https://dotnet.microsoft.com/download/dotnet-framework/net48

    I'm also considering moving from .Net Framework to .Net Core over time, so a different runtime may be required.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.28.1">
    1. Added config base xml for a18 beta into ConfigEditor.
    2. Added function to delete into Backup Editor.
     2.1 This feature has not yet been fully verified.
  </update>
  <update version="2.2.27.0">
    1. Backup function (Backup Editor) has been installed as a beta.
     1.1 Please enable beta mode from the settings, if you want to enable Backup Editor.
     1.2 Backup Editor can be started from the "Tool".
     1.3 Do not use backup while the server is running.
    2. Fixed a crash on "Initialize Settings" that occurred when Steam was not installed.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.26.9b">
    1. Fixed the internal code of the network library. This improves stability slightly.
    2. Fixed other internal code.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.25.8b">
    1. fixed that raise exception on ConfigEditor.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.24.7b">
    1. fixed config template for a17.2 on ConfigEditor.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.23.6b">
    1. fixed that remove chat text after input chat.
    2. fixed that dispose all when application exited.
    3. fixed an issue that not be able to get chat message on a17.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.22.5b">
    1. Update template configs for a17.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.21.4b">
    1. Update some libs.
    2. Changed version of .Net Framework to 4.7.1.
    3. Provisional support to a17.
     3.1 Changed to the method of copying config to executable file location.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.20.3b">
    1. Fixed an issue not to show English on updator detail.
    2. Fixed a bug that the process was not killed due to forced termination due to error.
    3. Fixed a bug that crashes in the initializer if Steam is not installed.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.19.2b">
    1. Added an updator.
    2. Added a system to get external and local ip address.
    3. Added a system to check port opened or not.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.18.1b">
    1. Fixed an issue that crash when click icon on window..
    2. Included Styles and some codes of KimamaLib and Excluded KimamaLib.
    3. Fixed an issue that crash when open the alert window.
  </update>
  <update version="2.1.17.0b">
    1. Fixed a bug that shift if empty property was found in ConfigEditor.
    2. Fixed a bug that server startup and Telnet are not worked correctly by it.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.17.17b">
    1. Fixed templates on ConfigEditor
    　Fixed english version template.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.16.16b">
    1. Fixed templates on ConfigEditor
    　Fixed an issue that the server could not be started by new file.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.15.15b">
    1. Added data on ConfigEditor for a16.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.14.14b">
    1. Fixed a bug that header information is not displayed in player list.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.13.13b">
    1. Added a function of shortcut key.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.12.12b">
    1. Fixed an issue that player acquisition and time acquisition do not work well.
    2. Added an option to check for updates at startup.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.11.11b">
    1. Fixed an issue is displaying Start Button when you push "Connect with Telnet" button
    2. Changed copyright year.
    3. Added a button to select file on initializing window.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.10.10b">
    1. Fixed an issue get an error when there are decimals in window size of settings.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.9.9b">
    1. Added a15 settings file for ConfigEditor.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.8.8b">
    1. Fixed an issue which could not get chat.

    2. Fixed an issue which initial version was old on ConfigEditor.

    3. Added Updater.

    4. Preparing for the next update.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.7.7b">
    1. Fixed an issue that could not open Admin window.

    2. Fixed an issue that get an error when select data there is not in the item on ConfigEditor.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.6.6b">
    1. Added an initialize setting.

    2. Added a button to remove logs.

    3. Added a14 file of ConfigEditor
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.5.5b">
    1. Reduced a length of log and added a function to set your length.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.4.4b">
    1. Changed a way to write console log
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.3.3b">
    1. Support functions to get and set time in game.

    2. Changed a code to using public library.

    3. Reduced using thread.

    4. Fixed Telnet.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.2.2b">
    1. Fixed some issues.

    2. Fixed Config Editor

    3. Support in English.
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.1.1b">
    1. FIxed an issue that selecting path function didnt work.

    2. Fixed an issue that clear path on setting then click cancel button.

    3. Added a function to hide the password

    4. Added Command list

    5. Remake ConfigEditor
  </update>
  <update version="1.0.0.0b">
    Savannah Manager 2 was released.
  </update>
</updates>
